

CONTACT

Phone: 647-822-3042

E-mail: clement.sung7@gmail.com Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/clement-sung7

Site: github.com/clembrulee

Portfolio:

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team player
Reliable and professional
Accommodating
Organized
Adaptable and Flexible
Time management
Fast learner
Motivated
Critical Analysis
Problem Solving

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3

Javascript(ES6)

React

Firebase

Responsive design

Website accessibility requirements

Version control using Git and Github

Paired programming

Team-based development

Project Scope Management

Microsoft Office(Word, Excel)

Labware LIMS software (3 years)

Empower software (2 years)

CLEMENT SUNG

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I am a front-end web developer with experience building web applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Firebase and API integrations. I have a background in chemistry and have worked in the lab for the past 5 years where I have developed adaptability, critical analysis, and attention to detail skills that I can apply to creating clean, responsive, and accessible web applications/solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OUALITY CONTROL ANALYST

Estee Lauder Companies Inc. | Dec 2019 - Mar 2021

- Performed analytical testing of in-process materials and raw materials on daily basis(10-15 samples per day) to meet release targets.
- Wrote comprehensive reports for out-of-specification results, deviations, and corrective and preventative action plans while managing time to perform daily analytical testing.
- Aided the team in daily routine instrument calibrations and analytical tests to maintain workflow.

QUALITY CONTROL CHEMIST

Apotex Inc | Feb 2016 - Dec 2019

- Performed HPLC (dissolution, assay, content uniformity), IR, UV, Karl-Fischer titration, and wet chemistry tests on various drug products on a daily basis (6-20 samples per day depending on test).
- Review chemists' documented work through LIMS software prior to releasing the product to market.
- Worked in a QC lab following GMP/GLP to adhere to regulatory bodies such as Health Canada and FDA and successfully completed 4+ audits

PROJECTS

Cratediggers

HTML |SCSS| Javascript Paired programming project created to recommend music artists based on a user's artist search or genre

Live / Repo

Hikari

React|CSS React project created to recommend anime shows/movies to the user.

Live / Repo

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE BOOTCAMP Juno College | Apr 2021 - June 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CHEMISTRY (BSC) Ryerson University | Sep 2010 - Apr 2015